[
    {
        "question": "How many people are in the band Tame Impala?",
        "answer": "one"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who gave the gettysburg address?",
        "answer": "Abraham Lincoln"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which music artist posted hatefull comments on twitter?",
        "answer": "Kanye West"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the slang word for charisma?",
        "answer": "rizz"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whos the best NBA player",
        "answer": "Lebron James"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the biggest Streamer?",
        "answer": "Caseoh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang the mostly hated song thick of it?",
        "answer": "KSI"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which School club has Reddit humor?",
        "answer": "Band kids"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hides in a cardboard box?",
        "answer": "Solid Snake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most no skill super smash bros character?",
        "answer": "Ridley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which kids show is rated better on IMDB that the hit TV show Breaking Bad?",
        "answer": "Bluey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the land of water under the US Between mexico and the US?",
        "answer": "Gulf of Mexico (I will deadname it)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which song by Green Day has gained popularity since September of 2024?",
        "answer": "American Idiot"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which video game can you fight godzilla while Hatsune Miku is hitting the Griddy?",
        "answer": "Fortnite"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mr Mcgarrah said which brain rot word when talking about how he got married?",
        "answer": "Rizz “I got that rizz” -McGarrah"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whats the most popular Laufey Song?",
        "answer": "From the start"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Brawlers are there in brawl stars?",
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the highest Elixir Card in Clash Royale?",
        "answer": "Mirror"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Troop has the highest HP in Clash royale?",
        "answer": "Golem (With Royal Chef Mirrored)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whats the highest possible health in Brawl Stars?",
        "answer": "Frank (Sheild Gear, Health Starpower)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which band released the song 'No Surprises'?",
        "answer": "Radiohead"
    }
]